Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1214, 1 fragment 05.5 x 14.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1214)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1215, 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1215)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1217, 1 fragment 08.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1217)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1218, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1218)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1223, 1 fragment 07.0 x 17.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1223)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1224, 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1224)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1225, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1225)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1226, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1226)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1227, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1227)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1228, 1 fragment 08.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1228)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1229, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1229)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1230, 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1230)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1231, 1 fragment 04.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1231)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1233, 1 fragment 09.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1233)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1234, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1234)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1235, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1235)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1236, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1236)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1237, 1 fragment 11.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1237)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1238, 1 fragment 13.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1238)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1239.01, 1 fragment 15.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1239.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1239.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1239.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1239.03, 1 fragment 03.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1239.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1240, 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1240)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1241, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1241)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1242, 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1242)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1243, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1243)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1244, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1244)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1246, 1 fragment 08.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1246)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1247, 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1247)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1248, 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1248)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1249, 1 fragment 09.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1249)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1250, 1 fragment 14.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1250)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1251, 1 fragment 13.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1251)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1252, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1252)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1253, 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1253)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1254, 1 fragment 02.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1254)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1255, 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1255)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1256, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1256)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1258, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1258)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1259, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1259)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1260, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1260)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1261, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1261)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1262, 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1262)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1263, 1 fragment 05.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1263)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1264, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1264)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1265, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1265)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1266, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1266)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1267.01, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1267.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1267.02, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1267.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1268.01, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1268.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1268.02, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1268.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1269, 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1269)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1270, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1270)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1271, 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1271)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1272, 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1272)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1273, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1273)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1274, 1 fragment 08.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1274)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1275, 1 fragment 03.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1275)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1276, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1276)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1277, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1277)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1278, 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1278)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1279, 1 fragment 03.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1279)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1280, 1 fragment 06.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1280)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1281, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1281)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1282.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1282.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1282.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1282.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1283, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1283)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1284, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1284)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1285.01, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1285.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1285.02, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1285.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1286, 1 fragment 20.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1286)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1287, 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1287)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1288, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1288)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1289, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1289)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1290, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1290)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1291, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1291)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1292, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1292)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1293, 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1293)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1294, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1294)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1295, 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1295)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1296, 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1296)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1297, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1297)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1298, 1 fragment 09.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1298)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1299, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1299)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1300, 1 fragment 06.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1300)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1301, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1301)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1302, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1302)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1303, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1303)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1304, 1 fragment 04.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1304)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1305, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1305)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1306, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1306)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1307, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1307)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1308.01, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1308.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1308.02, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1308.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1309, 1 fragment 07.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1309)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1310, 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1310)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1311, 1 fragment 04.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1311)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1312, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1312)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1313, 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1313)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1314, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1314)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1315, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1315)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1316, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1316)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1317, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1317)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1318, 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1318)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1319, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1319)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1320, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1320)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1321, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1321)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1322, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1322)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1323, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1323)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1324, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1324)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1325, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1325)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1326, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1326)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1327, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1327)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1328, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1328)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1329, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1329)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1330, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1330)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1331, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1331)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1332, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1332)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1333.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1333.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1333.02, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1333.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1334, 1 fragment 05.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1334)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1335, 1 fragment 08.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1335)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1336, 1 fragment 06.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1336)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1337, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1337)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1338, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1338)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1339, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1339)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1340, 1 fragment 00.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1340)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1341, 1 fragment 16.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1341)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1342, 1 fragment 01.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1342)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1343, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1343)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1344, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1344)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1346, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1346)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1347, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1347)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1348.01, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1348.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1348.02, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1348.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1349, 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1349)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1350, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1350)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1351, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1351)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1352, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1352)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1353, 1 fragment 03.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1353)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1354, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1354)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1355.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1355.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1355.02, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1355.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1356, 1 fragment 02.0 x 0.20 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1356)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1357, 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1357)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1358, 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1358)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1359, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1359)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1360, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1360)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1361, 1 fragment 07.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1361)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1362, 1 fragment 04.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1362)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1363.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1363.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1363.02, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1363.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1364, 1 fragment 02.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1364)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1365, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1365)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1366, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1366)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1367, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1367)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1368, 1 fragment 07.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1368)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1369, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1369)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1370, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1370)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1371, 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1371)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1372, 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1372)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1373, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1373)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1374, 1 fragment 11.5 x 21.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1374)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1375, 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1375)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1376, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1376)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1377, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1377)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1378, 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1378)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1379, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1379)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1380, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1380)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1381, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1381)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1382, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1382)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1383, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1383)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1384, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1384)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1385, 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1385)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1386, 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1386)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1387, 1 fragment 04.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1387)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1388, 1 fragment 11.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1388)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1389, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1389)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1390, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1390)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1391, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1391)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1392, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1392)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1393, 1 fragment 11.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1393)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1394, 1 fragment 10.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1394)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1395, 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1395)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1396, 1 fragment 14.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1396)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1397.01, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1397.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1397.02, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1397.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1398, 1 fragment 08.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1398)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1399, 1 fragment 09.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1399)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1400, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1400)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1401, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1401)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1404, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1404)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1405, 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1405)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1406.01, 1 fragment 06.0 x 16.0 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 1406.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1406.02, 1 fragment 10.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 1406.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1407, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1407)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1408, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1408)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1409, 1 fragment 01.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1409)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1410, 1 fragment 09.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1410)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1411, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1411)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1412, 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1412)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1413, 1 fragment 05.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1413)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1414, 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1414)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1415, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1415)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1416, 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1416)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1417, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1417)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1418, 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1418)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1419, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1419)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1420, 1 fragment 00.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1420)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1421, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1421)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1422, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1422)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1423, 1 fragment 00.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1423)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1424, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1424)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1425.01, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1425.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1425.02, 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1425.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1426, 1 fragment 08.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1426)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1427, 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1427)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1428.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1428.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1428.02, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1428.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1429, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1429)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1430, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1430)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1431, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1431)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1432, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1432)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1433, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1433)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1434.01, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1434.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1434.02, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1434.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1435, 1 fragment 08.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1435)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1436, 1 fragment 11.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1436)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1437, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1437)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1438, 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1438)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1439, 1 fragment 04.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1439)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1440, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1440)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1441, 1 fragment 05.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1441)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1442, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1442)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1443, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1443)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1444, 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1444)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1445, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1445)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1446, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1446)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1447, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1447)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1448, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1448)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1449, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1449)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1450, 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1450)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1451, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1451)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1452, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1452)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1453, 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1453)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1454, 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1454)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1455, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1455)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1456, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1456)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1457, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1457)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1458, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1458)